[{"id": 167, "question": "Directions: Read the following passage. The passage is followed by several questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A,B,C and D. Choose the one that fits best according to the information given in the passage. It may be open to discussion which city is the most beautiful in the world. But in terms of \" the most livable\", Melbourne has ranked top in a survey done by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) in August. In fact, four cities Down Under are among the top ten most livable cities. The climate in Australia is warm and mild, particularly in major coastal cities. As a result, people spend much time outdoors. They go to the beach, to the countryside, or play sports outdoors in fields. Take Melbourne for example. The city features many open green ...\n\nQ: What is the article mainly about?", "options": ["Multiculturalism in Australia.", "Qualities that make Australia stand out as \"the most livable\" place in the world.", "The comfortable environment and lifestyle in Australia.", "The world's most livable city, Melbourne."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1118, "question": "\"Migrant workers\" is a familiar term for 17-year-old Shi Jian. Her father and uncle often talk about the problems surrounding this group of people. However, Shi cares more about the children of these migrant workers. Last year Shi's housekeeper's daughter had to give up her schooling in Beijing because she would not be allowed to sit the national college entrance exam. She was forced to continue her high school education in her hometown in Sichuan Province. Shi thinks the current law is unfair for migrant workers' children, as it prevents them from studying at public schools, unless their parents pay huge sums. So, Shi decided to do a survey of migrant workers so that she could find some solutions to help solve the problem. In the last six months Shi spoke to 186 migrant workers in Beijing...\n\nQ: All of the following prevent migrant worker's kids from attending schools in cities EXCEPT  _", "options": ["their parents' low income", "their lack of confidence to face the fierce competitions in city schools", "school's high tuitions", "that schools for migrant workers' children may close or relocate"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3305, "question": "In the 19thcentury, Americans from the eastern states moved out west to settle in the rich new lands along the Pacific Coast. The most difficult part of their trip was crossing \"the Great American Desert\" in the western part of the United States by horse and wagon. The western desert can be very dangerous. There is little water and there are few trees. But the desert also has scenery of great beauty. Tall towers of red and yellow stone rise sharply from the flat, sandy valley floor. The scene has been photographed many times and appears in movies and on TV. In Arizona, man-made dams across the Colorado River have made two large lakes in the middle of the dry desert country. At Lake Powell, the red stone arch of Rainbow Bridge rises high above the blue lake. There are few roads. Many areas ...\n\nQ: In the 19thcentury, Americans moved from east to west because they  _  .", "options": ["enjoyed the trip", "wanted to make their home there", "wanted to find new grassland there", "had no water to drink"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2729, "question": "Manchester is the \"capital\" of the northwest of England. Situated on the east bank of the River Irwell, it is a lively busy city with a large student population. Although it was once seen as only a dull industrial place, in recent years Manchester has become the \"in\" place. It is well-known for its clubs, its fashion and its music, not to mention its world -famous football team, Manchester United. There is plenty to see in Manchester and something to suit all taste. For example, you have a taste of the Orient in Chinatown, home to Manchester's large Chinese population. Another place to visit is the historical Eastlefield area, which contains the first urban heritage park in Britain. Here you can walk around the museums and experience the atmosphere of the 19thcentury Manchester. Football f...\n\nQ: If you are interested in history,   _   in Manchester.", "options": ["you will see the 18 thcentury center building", "you can go to Chinatown", "you don't have a big choice", "you can visit the Eastlefield"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 949, "question": "You can never be too sure these days in the United States of your neighbours or even your customers! Try to keep a low profile in your neighborhood: don't announce to just about everyone that you are running a home business with thousands of dollars worth of equipment. As much as possible, don't invite clients or visitors to your home. In fact I know of some home-based entrepreneurs who would rather meet their clients in a neutral ground, e.g. the client's office or even Starbucks. There are other ways to keep burglars away from your house. *Keep lights on around your house in the evenings. Light is a natural fright for burglars. *Invest in a security alarm, particularly if your house is located in a remote spot. Security systems can often bring down the cost of your homeowner's insurance ...\n\nQ: The advice given by the writer in the passage focuses on   _  .", "options": ["how to make your house safer from burglars", "what to do when your house is broken into", "how to improve social security in the United States", "how to run a home business"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 985, "question": "People can be addicted to different things -- e.g. alcohol, drug, certain foods, or even television. People who have such an addiction are compulsive :They have a very powerful psychological need that they feel they must satisfy. According to psychologists, many people are compulsive spenders. They feel that they must spend money. This compulsion, like most others, is impossible to explain reasonably. For compulsive spenders who buy on credit , charge accounts are even more exciting than money. In other words, compulsive spenders feel that with credit, they can do anything. Their pleasure in spending large amounts is actually greater than the pleasure that they get from the things they buy. There is even a special psychology of bargain hunting. To save money, of course, most people look fo...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE according to the text?", "options": ["People spend money for exactly the same reason that they need to buy things.", "Business people and advertisers can use the psychology of people's spending habits to increase sales.", "Business people understand the psychology of compulsive buying better than scientists do.", "Compulsive bargain hunters do not have problems with money."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3115, "question": "Lindsay Morgan Lohan was born on July 2, 1986. She was such a natural beauty that she began modeling at the age of 3, and because of her natural talent, she played parts in over 60 TV commercials for companies such as Abercrombie & Fitch, Wendy's, the Gap, Pizza Hut, Calvin Klein, and Jell-O, in which she shared the screen with Bill Cosby. When she was 7, Lohan was required to dress up as garbage for a Halloween short play on the Late Show with David Letterman called \"Things You Find on the Bottom of the Subway.\" It was her first real acting job. In 1996, Lohan got her second big _ when she was given a role on the long-running NBC soap opera \"Another World.\" For only one season, she became the third actress to act the part Alexandra Alli Fowler. Shortly after, she hit the highway to fame w...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT the job that Lohan has done until now?", "options": ["A singer.", "An actress.", "A model.", "A dancer."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1565, "question": "Sports, drama, and a variety of organizations keep students busy during high school. Where do they find the money to do these things? Not everyone gets it from Mommy and Daddy. Most have to pay for these activities. Some adults question if high school students should have jobs. Some people worry that teens with after-school jobs will struggle to find time for homework. Actually, the responsibility of having a job helps teens prioritize their time. Many jobs take only a couple of hour shifts on weeknights. According to a survey, 86 percent of high school students have an after-school, weekend or summer job and students who work between 10 and 20 hours per week during the school year have statistically higher grades-point averages than those who do not work at all. Those who work in high sch...\n\nQ: According to the survey, compared with those who don't work, teens with after-school jobs are  _  .", "options": ["more likely to go to college", "usually doing better at school", "more willing to pay for their education", "able to find a better job after graduation"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1531, "question": "Conventional wisdom is a major barrier to innovation that threatens the survival of companies everywhere.It's based on the assumption that old ideas will always work,so they shouldn't be challenged. While this may be a valid assumption in situations that don't change,it's unlikely to hold true in a changing situation.In today's rapid changing global environment,old methods often don't work,and stubbornly using them can lead to major problems. Most people seem to agree with conventional wisdom because it gives one a false sense of security.If everyone else believes it,then it must be true.Individuals who use conventional wisdom are certain that they are right,and being right is good. They want to continue using old ideas rather than take risks with changes that might not work.In 1977,Ken Ol...\n\nQ: The founding of CNN is used as an example to prove   _  .", "options": ["missing opportunities could lead to failure", "changing could contribute to business success", "watching news at the dinner hour is convenient", "conventional wisdom influences business success"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3073, "question": "In our daily life, many of us feel stressed more or less. Some like this pressure and work better because of it. Others are not comfortable with any stress at alls they soon become unhappy if they feel stressed. Sometimes stress can lead people to do things they wouldn't usually do, such as overeat, smoke, drink, or use drugs. Streas, however, is a very normal part of life. It is important to understand that stress doesn't come from an event itself, that is, from the things that are happening in our lives. It comes from the meaning we give to what has happened. For example, a crying baby may be stressful to one person, but it may not bother another person at all, a traffic jam may be stressful to one person while another person may be able to stay calm. We can experience stress any time we...\n\nQ: The author mentions the example of crying baby in order to  _", "options": ["explain that stress is everywhere", "tell different people react to stress differently", "help people learn that stress comes from an event", "give the definition of stress."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1470, "question": "Wal-Mart is not just the world's largest retailer . It's the world's largest company, which sells in three months what number-two retailer Home Depot sells in a year. Wal-Mart exercises its power for just one purpose: to bring the lowest possible prices to its customers. At Wal-Mart, that goal is never reached. The retailer has a clear policy for suppliers: On basic products that don't change, the price Wal-Mart will pay, and will charge shoppers, must drop year after year. But what almost no one outside the world of Wal-Mart and none of its 21,000 suppliers know is the high cost of those low prices. To survive in the face of its pricing demands, makers of everything from bikes to jeans have had to close US plants in favor of obtaining products from abroad. Indeed, the real story of Wal-Ma...\n\nQ: How do suppliers meet the requirements of Wal-Mart?", "options": ["To sell even more goods in three months.", "To cut down the employment rate sharply.", "To charge shoppers at a much higher price.", "To run the business in a well-organized way."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2655, "question": "Kabul,Oct.28 (Xinhuanet)--- Unknown armed men in military uniform kidnapped three staff of the United Nations in the Afghan capital city at broad daylight Thursday ,Afghan officials confirmed . \"Three armed men in military uniform _ a UN car in Baraki area ofprefix = st1 /Kabulcity early afternoon and took away three persons including two women with them, \"Rohullah, a witness at the site told Xinhua. The kidnappers also badly beat up the Afghan driver of the UN car, added Rohullah who is a lorry driver in the city. The area has been watched over by UN guards. UN officials as well as Afghan confirmed the incident but refused to provide further information. The three kidnapped , according to some officials , who are from Britain, Ireland and Kosovo, were working for the UN-sponsored Joint El...\n\nQ: What is the best title of the news report ?", "options": ["Successful Presidential Election in Afghan", "US-led Troops Acting in Afghan", "Holy War in Afghan", "3 UN staff kidnapped in Kabul"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2666, "question": "New York City schoolchildren can't use cellphones at school because of Mayor Michael R. Bloomberg's ban on cellphones in schools. Many parents are opposed to Mayor Michael R. Bloomberg's ban on cellphones in schools by e-mail messages. There was a 13-year-old student who was shot with a gun after school, unable to call his mother for help. There was a high school student robbed three times last year, twice in her school building. There was a girl who got a piece of glass placed in her eye during school and was saved from a possible cornea transplant only because, having disobeyed the cellphone ban, she was able to call her mother and get an operation on time. The ban has been on for years, but it set off a widespread parental outcry only in April, after some headmasters sent home letters r...\n\nQ: A 13-year-old student was shot with a gun after school, unable to call his mother for help, because   _  .", "options": ["his mother had no cellphone", "his mother wasn't at home", "he didn't take a cellphone with him", "he was too frightened to call"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 930, "question": "London Heathrow is the biggest airport in the UK, and it also handles more international passenger traffic than any other airport in the world. For this reason, enlargement was planned and on 27th March a fifth terminal opened to help to deal with the many passengers that pass through the airport. The new terminal has taken a long time to plan and build. The idea was first proposed back in the 1980s. The opening of it has been talked about widely in the media in the UK and expectations were high for the PS4.3 billion project. However, in spite of long preparations at Terminal 5 ahead of the grand opening, things soon went into a mess. There were problems from the very beginning as staff had difficulties finding car parking spaces and getting through security to get into the building. This ...\n\nQ: What is the best title of the passage?", "options": ["London Heathrow Terminal 5.", "The First Day of Heathrow Terminal 5.", "A New Star for Heathrow Terminal 5.", "A Dark History of Heathrow Terminal 5."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2571, "question": "The first reality TV show in the world was called Expedition Robinson and it was shown in Sweden in 1997. Half the population of the country watched the final event and a new kind of TV program was born. Two years later in Holland , the first series of Big Brother was filmed. Again, it was a great success and the final program was watched by 15 million people. Now more than 20 countries around the world have Big Brother or Expedition Robinson on their TV screens. The ordinary people who take part in the programs are known by millions of people in their own countries and reality TV has become big, big business. For the TV producers, reality TV is a dream come true because many of the programs cost nothing to make. At some point, the television viewers are asked to telephone the program to v...\n\nQ: Those who take part in the reality TV shows are usually   _  .", "options": ["common people", "pop TV stars", "attractive people", "famous film stars"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1691, "question": "Long long ago, there was a man who was good at shooting arrows.He asked the king to declare him as the greatest archer of the country.The king was about to do so when an old servant of the king said,\"Wait,sir.I know an old man who lives in the forest.He is a much greater archer.Let this young man go to him and learn from him for at least three years.\" The man could not believe what the servant said,but he went and found the old man and he was! For three years he learned from him.Then one day,when he thought he had learned everything,the thought arose in him:\"If I kill this old man,then I will be the greatest archer.\" The old man had gone to cut wood and he was coming back carrying wood on his shoulder.The young man hid behind a tree,waiting to kill him.He shot an arrow.The old man took a s...\n\nQ: What lesson can you learn from the story?", "options": ["Always use a piece of wood to protect yourself from an arrow.", "You must never try to become better than your teacher.", "The older a man is,the better archer he usually becomes.", "There's always someone better than you in this world."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1749, "question": "Where is that noise coming from? Not sure? Try living with your eyes closed for a few years. Blind people are better at locating sounds than people who can see, a new study says, without the benefits of vision the ears seem to work much better. Previous studies have shown that blind people are better than others at reaching out and touching the sources of sounds that are close by. Researchers from the University of Montreal wanted to see if blind people were also better at locating sounds that are far away. Twenty-three blind people participated in the study. All had been sightless for at least 20 years. Fourteen of them had lost their vision before age 11. the rest went blind after age 16. The experiment also included 10 people who could see but were wearing blind-folds. In one task, volu...\n\nQ: If people were asked to tell the direction of a sound from the side, who would perform best?", "options": ["Those who are blind.", "Those who have gone blind since children.", "Those who went blind at age 16.", "Those who are blindfolded."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3138, "question": "Harry potter and The Hunger Games haven't been big hits for nothing. Lots of teens still read quite a lot. But a study shows a clear decrease over time. Nearly half of 17-year-olds say they read for pleasure no more than one or two times a year. That's way down from ten years ago. The digital revolution means there are more platforms than ever to read on. Jim Steyer has been studying the effect of technology on children. He has four kids and has seen the trend most with his 16-year-old. \"I start to see it in our 10-year-old as well, because he is reading less and less, and more and more attracted to some of the digital media platforms that he has access to, and that he didn't have access to when he was 6 or 7 years old,\" he says. The studies don't say that kids are reading less because the...\n\nQ: What did Jim Steyer see in his four kids?", "options": ["They tend to read more on electronic devices.", "They created their own digital media platform.", "They improved their reading on electronic devices.", "They have become more addicted to digital media."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1866, "question": "My father always told me never to ever reveal my true opinions towards other people unless such opinions are positive. He said this is the \"Chu Shi Zhe Xue\", the philosophy of dealing with social network. It seems that everybody here just follows this philosophy very, very well. I would say that if I were given true friendship I would definitely treasure it with my greatest care. If I really regard someone as my close friend, I would never leave her alone whenever she's in need, either financially or mentally. And I always believe, as long as I treat people with whole-hearted honesty, I would have some rewards--at least, just ONE true friend of the same gender. Sometimes I just miss my friends in China. Perhaps when we became friends, we were still young, too young to have been polluted by...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements about the writer is not TRUE?", "options": ["She is now living abroad but doesn't enjoy the life there.", "She sometimes doubts her father's philosophy.", "She shows a positive attitude to her relationship with others.", "She doesn't think highly of her friends by saying \"They are good\"."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 13, "question": "Bungee jumping is an activity about jumping from a tall structure while connected to a large elastic cord . The tall structure is usually a fixed object, such as a building, bridge or crane; but it is also possible to jump from a movable object, such as a hot-air balloon or helicopter, that has the ability to stay over one place on the ground; fixed-wing aircraft are unsuitable because they only stay high when moving quickly forward. When the person jumps, the cord stretches to absorb the energy of the fall, then the jumper flies upwards again as the cord jumps back. The jumper oscillates up and down until all the energy is used up. The word bungee first appeared around 1930 and was the name for a rubber eraser. The first modern bungee jumps were made on 1 April 1979 from the 250-foot Clif...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT suitable for bungee jumping?", "options": ["The fixed-wing aircraft", "The helicopter", "The hot-air balloon", "The mobile crane"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 418, "question": "The day the letter arrived from my university telling me how much I owed them for my first semester, I felt a lump forming in my throat. I hadn't even started my degree and already I was in debt. But although the sum was unsettling, I had peace of mind: I had taken out a loan that would cover the next three years of tuition fees and living expenses. A government body in the UK, the Student Loans Company, provides loans to students whose parents cannot afford to cover the costs themselves. Students forward this amount to the university in advance and agree to repay the loan when they begin their first job. For me, it was a lot of money -around &6,000(60,860 Yuan) per year in total -and much more than I had ever been responsible for. I would receive a couple of thousand pounds per semester -...\n\nQ: How did the writer feel when the letter arrived?", "options": ["Unsettled.", "Calm.", "Relieved.", "Stressed."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3252, "question": "Most people buy a lot of gifts just before Christmas. But some people think we buy too much. They have started a special day called Buy Nothing Day. They don't want anyone to go shopping on that day. Buy Nothing Day is November 29. It's 25 days before Christmas. It's after Thanksgiving Day and often the first day of Christmas shopping. At this time, we see ads in Newspapers and on TV telling us to \"buy, buy, buy!\" The idea for Buy Nothing Day started in Vancouver, British Columbia. Now people all over the world celebrate Buy Nothing Day. In California, parents and children get together to read stories, sing songs, and paint pictures. The children talk about why they don't need a lot of toys. This year, in Manchester, England, people dressed up in costumes to tell people that we buy too muc...\n\nQ: What did the students do in New Mexico for the day?", "options": ["They donated the food of their own.", "They talked to others about it.", "They made some slogans for it.", "They organized a luxurious dinner."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3452, "question": "It was a physical class. But it was nothing like previous ones -- the class was \"attended\" by over 60 million students across China, and the teacher was not even on the planet: she was 340 kilometers above the earth. \"Hello, everyone. I'm Wang Yaping. I'll host your lecture today.\" Smiling to the camera, Wang, China's second female astronaut, started her video class on June 20 on board the Tiangong-1 space station. To show how Newton's Laws work in space, Wang and her fellow astronauts used simple items like balls and spinning tops. The highlight of the lecture was when Wang _ using a metal ring, something that only happens in zero gravity, where the surface tension of water is much higher than it is on the earth. She then took it a step further by pouring more water onto the film and turn...\n\nQ: Why is the class different from a common one?", "options": ["Because it took 40 minutes.", "Because over 60 million students across the world attended it.", "Because the teacher was on the planet.", "Because the lecturer was in space."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3206, "question": "People want action on noise, a recent public meeting in Brisbane showed.Some want technical improvements such as quieter air conditioners or better sound barriers around major roads.Others want tougher laws to restrict noise from building sites or to require owners to take responsibility for barking dogs.But the highest priority was a noise complaints system that works. Brisbane City Council receives more complaints about noise than all other problems put together.So it conducted a survey and found that about half its residents are upset by noise in one form or another -traffic, mowers, pool pumps, air conditioners or loud parties.This inspired the Council to bring together more than 100 citizens one evening to talk through a range of options. The meeting found the present regulatory syste...\n\nQ: According to the recent public meeting in Brisbane, what was the first step to take in order to reduce noise pollution?", "options": ["Produce quieter air conditioners.", "Provide better sound barriers around major roads.", "Establish a noise complaints system.", "Make stricter laws to require owners to take responsibility for barking dogs."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2621, "question": "In the dark and damp market,Chen ShuChu,near her sixties,owns a stall that her father left her.The stall,called YuanJin Vegetables,is her everything.Chen earns only a little money by selling vegetables,but she has donated about $321,550 to help poor children. In March,Forbes magazine named her one of the 48 great philanthropists from the AsiaPacific region.A month later,TIME magazine selected the year's top 100 influential people and Chen was one of them.Although she has received many honours and rewards,Chen only cares about her vegetable stall and whether her regular customers buy her vegetables or not.\"I do not place great importance on money.When I donate to help others,I feel happy and I can sleep well at night.\" Chen said. Chen's ability to donate such a great deal of money has led m...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true about Chen?", "options": ["Her vegetable stall is called YuanJin Vegetables.", "She is a famous philanthropist in China.", "She cares about what clothes she wears very much.", "Many people are surprised by Chen's donation."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1091, "question": "What does the word \"home\" mean to you? How do you say the word in French? In Spanish? In your language? Although people usually know what the word means, it often has no exact translation. It's not surprising really, because the idea of home differs from country to country, and from person to person. A home is more than a roof and four walls. It's the cooking, eating, talking, playing and family living that go on inside, which are important as well. And at home you usually feel safe and relaxed. But it's not just that homes look different in different countries, they also contain different things and reveal different attitudes and needs. For example, in cold northern Europe, there's a fire in the living room or kitchen and all the chairs face it. In the south, where the sun shines a lot an...\n\nQ: The word \"home\" has no exact translation because   _  .", "options": ["people can't find this word in the dictionary", "no one knows what it is", "it has different meanings in different countries", "people can't understand each other very well"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2775, "question": "How To Apply for USA Passports Online If you live in the United States, and you're planning a trip abroad, it is important to apply for new passports at least 2 months in advance (to avoid extra charges for an expedited passport processing). You can now get the application for a passport online. Some directions are detailed below: Downloading the passport application: The USA passport application, Form DS-11, is available for download on the US Department of State's website. *The passport application form is a Portable Document Format (PDF) file, and your computer must have Adobe Acrobat Reader to open it. If you do not have Adobe Acrobat Reader, you must first download the Adobe Acrobat software. You can do so by clicking here. *If you would like to download a blank application, click her...\n\nQ: Which of the following is not required to be included in the application form?", "options": ["Your wife's / husband's name", "You blood type", "Your employer", "Your travel plans"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2254, "question": "Just getting accepted to an American college or university does not guarantee that you will get a visa. And getting a visa just lets you arrive in the United States. It does not guarantee that an immigration officer will permit you to enter the country. If you are requesting a visa for the first time, you will probably have to go to an American embassy or consulate . You will need to bring a government form sent to you by your American school that shows you have been accepted. You will also need banking and tax records that show you have enough money to pay for your education. And be prepared to provide evidence that you will return to your home country after your studies end. All of this is important in satisfying the requirements to get a visa. A consular official will also take your pic...\n\nQ: When should you apply for a visa?", "options": ["The moment you have been accepted to a school in the US.", "One hundred twenty days before you go to the US.", "Thirty days before classes begin.", "After the immigration officer permit you to enter the US."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1825, "question": "Thank-you cards -- heartfelt expressions of gratitude for gifts, services and general kindness -- seem to be rare in an age when the Internet continues to reduce human touch. Although our society has changed greatly over the past century, the _ of thank-you notes has not. While most people would agree that thank-you notes under these conditions are a necessity, there are still those who forever delay or are forgetful for unknown reasons. And at no time of the year are thank-you notes more visible (or lacking) than June, the month of graduations, and the beginning of summer parties. \" It' s a must-do thing. A real ' thank you' does not come by e-mail. It comes in the mail in an envelope. And what comes out of an envelope is a beautiful thing to touch and to handle and to pass around for eve...\n\nQ: The author implies in this article that   _  .", "options": ["old-fashioned people don't use e-mails", "the changing society is making people impolite and lazy", "modern technology is driving people apart", "the e-hyper world is not a nice place to live in"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 597, "question": "Poet William Stafford once said that we are defined more by the detours in life than by the narrow road toward goals.I like this image.But it was quite by accident that I discovered the deep meaning of his words. For years we made the long drive from our home in Seattle to my parents' home in Boise in nine hours.We traveled the way most people do:the fastest,shortest,easiest road,especially when I was alone with four noisy,restless kids who hate confinement and have strong opinions about everything. Road trips felt risky,so I would drive fast,stopping only when I had to.We would stick to the freeways and arrive tired. But then Banner,our lamb was born.He was rejected by his mama days before our planned trip to Boise.I had two choices:leave Banner with my husband,or take him with me.My husb...\n\nQ: The author stopped regularly on the country roads to  _  .", "options": ["relax in the fresh air", "take a deep breath", "take care of the lamb", "let the kids play with Banner"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 64, "question": "New research at Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis shows that people who struggle with mood problems or addiction can safely quit smoking and that kicking the habit is associated with improved mental health. Cavazos-Rehg, an assistant professor of psychiatry, found that quitting or significantly cutting back on cigarette smoking was linked to improved mental health outcomes. Quitting altogether or reducing by half the number of cigarettes smoked daily was associated with lower risk for mood disorders like depression, as well as a lower likelihood of alcohol and drug problems. \"We don't know if their mental health improves first and then they are more motivated to quit smoking or if quitting smoking leads to an improvement in mental health,\" Cavazos-Rehg said. \"But either...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["Smoking was associated with alcohol and drug problems.", "Quitting smoking may help to improve mental health.", "Smoking can lead to cancer or other deadly problems.", "Those who had mental problem are more motivated to quit smoking."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 4, "question": "There is probably no field of human activity in which our values and lifestyles are shown more clearly and strongly than they are in the clothes that we choose to wear.The dress of an individual is a kind of \"sign language\" that communicates a set of information and is usually the basis on which immediate impressions are formed.Traditionally,a concern for clothes was considered to be an affair of females,while men took pride in the fact that they were completely lacking in clothes consciousness . This type of American culture is by degrees changing as man dress takes on greater variety and color.Even as early as 1955,a researcher in Michigan said that _ White collar workers in particular viewed dress as a symbol of ability,which could be used to impress or influence others,especially in th...\n\nQ: Traditionally,people usually thought that   _  .", "options": ["men cared very much for clothes", "women were concerned greatly about what they wore while men didn't", "both men and women paid great attention to their clothes", "neither men nor women showed interest in clothes"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 590, "question": "It's a fact that we all dream. Some dreams seem to last for hours, others only for seconds. Some of us have strange dreams, some have interesting dreams, and some of us have unpleasant dreams. Tests in the 1980s showed that these dreams occur within 90-minute cycles, each cycle made up of six stages. In the last stage people experience rapid eye movement, known as REM, and it is in this stage that dreaming takes place. Eighty percent of people who were woken during this sixth stage could easily remember their dreams. On the other hand, when during the first five stages (NREM), only seven percent could describe a dream. However, of these same people woken during the first five stages, 74% were able to remember thinking activity, although they would not call it a dream. NerysDee, who has wri...\n\nQ: People woken during REM sleep can  _  .", "options": ["hardly remember their dreams", "easily remember their dreams", "only remember their dreams", "partly remember their thinking activity"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 818, "question": "Long after the 1998 World Cup was won, disappointed fans were still cursing the disputed refereeing decisions that denied victory to their team. A researcher was appointed to study the performance of some top referees. The researcher organized an experimental tournament involving four youth teams. Each match lasted an hour, divided into three periods of 20 minutes during which different referees were in charge. Observers noted down the referees' errors, of which there were 61 over the tournament. Converted to a standard match of 90 minutes, each referee made almost 23 mistakes, a remarkably high number. The researcher then studied the videotapes to analyse the matches in detail. Surprisingly, he found that errors were more likely when the referees were close to the incident. When the offic...\n\nQ: The experiment conducted by the researcher was meant to   _  .", "options": ["review the decisions of referees at the 1998 World Cup", "analyse the causes of errors made by football referees", "set a standard for football refereeing", "reexamine the rules for football refereeing"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 959, "question": "Finally, I entered the university. Because of my careful savings, I did not have to work during the school year. Then, summer came and it was time to work harder than ever. I continued working as a waitress at night, instructed tennis camps several mornings a week and worked as a secretary for a few hours in the afternoons. I even decided to take a class at a community college. This class at the community college saved me $650. It was an extremely tiring summer and made me anxious to return to my relatively easy life at the university. During my second and third years of undergraduate schooling, I decided to work about five hours per week in the campus admissions office answering phones. This provided a little spending money and kept me from drawing my savings out. The overall situation lo...\n\nQ: The writer took a class at a community college mainly because   _  .", "options": ["she wanted to save money", "life there was relatively easy", "summer time was tiring", "it was required by the university"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3153, "question": "Paul received an automobile from his brother as a Christmas present. On Christmas Eve when Paul came out of his office, a street boy was walking around the shiny new car, admiring it. \"Is this your car, Mister?\" he asked. Paul nodded. \"My brother gave it to me for Christmas.\" The boy was astonished. \"You mean your brother gave it to you and it didn't cost you anything? Boy, I wish....\" He hesitated. Of course Paul knew what he was going to wish for. He was going to wish he had a brother like that. But what the kid said made Paul quite surprised. \"I wish,\" the boy went on, \"that I could be a brother like that.\" Paul looked at the boy in astonishment, and then impulsively he added, \"Would you like to take a ride in my automobile?\" \"Oh, yes, I'd love that.\" After a short ride, the boy turned ...\n\nQ: What can we learn from the passage?   _  .", "options": ["Having a rich brother is important.", "It's unlucky to have a disabled brother.", "It's better to give than to receive.", "God helps those who help themselves."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1041, "question": "Do dogs understand us? Be careful what you say around your dog. It might understand more than you think. A _ named Rico recognizes the names of about 200 objects, say researchers in Germany. The dog also appears to be able to learn new words as easily as a 3-year-old child. Its word-learning skills are as good as those of a parrot or _ . In one experiment, the researchers took all 200 items that Rico is supposed to know and divided them into 20 groups of 10 objects. Then the owner told the dog to go and fetch one of the items and bring it back. In four tests, Rico got 37 out of 40 commands right. As the dog couldn't see anyone to get clues, the scientists believe Rico must understand the meanings of certain words. In another experiment, the scientists took one toy that Rico had never seen ...\n\nQ: What does the writer want to tell us?", "options": ["To train your dog.", "To talk with your dog.", "To be friendly to your dog.", "To be careful with your dog."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3394, "question": "Since the 1950s, most of the stars of pop music have come from Britain and America. Howver, in the last ten years, when many different kinds of music have established themselves on the pop scene, more and more stars have come from other countries. Pop music changes all the time and new stars appear and become famous. For a musician to stay popular and still produced good, original music over a long period of time, is a sign of true star. Most stars start their careers in a simple way---- playing in unknown night clubs or dance-hall where people want to dance to the music, not listen to it. They may have continued doing this for many years untill they get a \"break\"---- a chance to perform in a well -known place or get a recording contract. To become a star is the aim of every singer or musi...\n\nQ: According to the passage, a \"break\" may mean a chance to   _  .", "options": ["perform in a well-known concert", "get a recording contract", "play in dance-halls", "meet a lot of pop-crazy teenagers"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 549, "question": "Introductory Chemistry was taught at Duke University for many years by Professor Bonk.One year, two guys took the class and did pretty well on all the quizzes and midterms.They each had a solid A.These two friends were so confident in going into the final that the weekend before the final week, despite the Chemistry final being on Monday, they decided to go to the prefix = st1 /UniversityofVirginiato party with some friends. They had a great time there.However, with their hangovers and tiredness, they overslept all day Sunday and didn't make it back to Duke until early Monday morning.Rather than taking the final then, they found Professor Bonk after the final and explained to him how they missed the final.They told him they went up to the University of Virginia for the weekend and had plan...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["honesty is the best policy", "you should think twice before you jump", "one never loses anything by politeness", "he who makes no mistakes makes nothing"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3071, "question": "Ladji Doucoure of France beat Olympic champion Liu Xiang of China in the final meters to claim the title of the men's 110 meters hurdles at the 10thworld championships in Helsinki on Friday. Doucoure, who led the world this season with 12.97 seconds, over took the Chinese to win the race in 13.07 seconds. Liu was second in 13.08. Four-time world champion Allen Johnson of the United States took the third in 13.10. The 22-year-old Doucoure said after the race, \" I can not tell you just how long I have been dreaming of this. This victory is the result of a lot of hard work, and also a lot of support from people who have believed in me. I had a bad start, touched a few hurdles, but after the 4thhurdle I _ and went straight to the finish line.\" Liu, who won the Olympic gold with a world record-...\n\nQ: According to Sun Haiping, Liu Xiang might have won the gold if   _  .", "options": ["he had done better during his reaction period", "he had run the track next to Ladji Doucoure of Allen Johnson", "he had practiced clearance more before that race", "he hadn't touched a few hurdles in the race"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 245, "question": "Worn by the rich and famous around the world and now a $799.04 million-a-year enterprise , Ugg boots have come a long way since their 1973 creation--designed to keep surfers' feet warm in cold Australian conditions. Twenty-eight years after selling the rights to his woollen-lined creation, Aussie Ugg boot inventor Shane Stedman says he has no regrets though missing out on a great footwear fortune . A lifelong surfer, Mr. Stedman, now 69, who lives at beachside Mona Vale in Sydney, said his invention grew from need. \"The sea is bloody cold in the Aussie winter...I used to wear football jerseys to keep them (feet) warm\", Mr. Stedman said. But his sheepskin invention soon solved the problem and Mr. Stedman went on to spend a decade selling the sturdy boots, until 1983 when he sold the rights ...\n\nQ: The text mainly tells us that   _  .", "options": ["Ugg inventor is unwilling to sell his rights", "Ugg inventor is happy to trade dollars for surfing", "Ugg boots were made of special materials", "Ugg boots were invented specially to surfers"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1095, "question": "College visits are important.Before you commit years of your life and money to a school, be sure you're choosing a place,\" that is a good match for your personality and interests.You can't get the \"feel' of a school from any guidebook, so be sure to visit the campus.Below are a few tips for getting the most out of your college visit. 1.Explore on your own Of course you should take the official campus tour, but be sure to allow time to hang around on your own. The trained tour guides will show you a school's selling points.But the 1dest and prettiest buildings don't give you the entire picture of a college.Try to walk the extra mile and get the complete picture of the campus. 2.Read the Bulletin Boards When you visit the student center, academic buildings and residence hall, take a few minu...\n\nQ: Reading the bulletin boards can help you  _  .", "options": ["decide the major you want to study", "find out the after-class activities on campus", "get free coupons from the admission offices", "find out the options of healthy food"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2650, "question": "Collections were the inspiration for a project at Thomas Tallis School, which formed part of the Imagine Children's Literature Festival last autumn. Each child (aged 12-13) beatified a box and wrote a story on the subject of collections to throw inside it. The boxes were spread within the Royal Festival Hall's Ballroom. Some were left empty to encourage The subject chosen by Luren was an imaginative one. \"It's a sort o f Cinderella story,\" she told me, inspired by a collection of letters from her cousin, ha the story these become love letters, burned by a creel stepmother. Lauren's best friend Charlotte is the stepmother. \"I'm in Charlotte's story too,\" says Lauren, \"and I get run over.\" Charlotte's tale was inspired by the girls' coin collection. \"We've collected foreign coins for years -...\n\nQ: Millie Murray thinks   _  .", "options": ["collections could inspire writing creativity", "it was good for parents to have collections", "inspirations were very useful in writing stories", "setting collection subjects restricted inspirations"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1670, "question": "In 1905, as part of his Special Theory of Relativity, Albert Einstein published the point that a large amount of energy could be released from a small amount of matter. This was expressed by the equation E = mc2. But bombs were not what Einstein had in mind when he published this equation. In 1929, he publicly declared that if a war broke out he would \"refuse to do war service, direct or indirect....\" His position would change in 1933, as the result of Adolf Hitler's coming into power in Germany. Einstein's greatest role in the invention of the atomic bomb was signing a letter to President Franklin Roosevelt urging that the bomb be built because some physicists feared that Germany might be working on an atomic bomb. Among those concerned were physicists Leo Szilard and Eugene Wigner. But t...\n\nQ: Einstein realized his mistake in   _  .", "options": ["co-operating with his workmates", "inventing the atomic bomb", "publishing his equation", "signing the letter to Roosevelt"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1418, "question": "Farmer Joe was in his cart when he was hit by a truck. He decided his injuries from the accident were serious enough to take the trucking company to court. In court the trucking company's lawyer was questioning farmer Joe. \"Didn't you say, at the scene of the accident, 'I'm fine'?\" said the lawyer. Farmer Joe responded, \"Well, I'll tell you what happened. I had just loaded my favorite donkey Bessie into the....\" \"I didn't ask for any details,\" the lawyer interrupted, \"just answer the question. Didn't you say, at the scene of the accident, 'I'm fine'?\" Farmer Joe said, \"Well I had just got Bessie into the cart and I was driving down the road....\" The lawyer interrupted again and said, \"Judge, I am trying to establish the fact that, at the scene of the accident, this man told the highway pol...\n\nQ: The trucking company's lawyer insisted Farmer Joe answer his question   _  .", "options": ["because he wasn't sure whether Farmer Joe was hurt in the accident", "so as to prove that Farmer Joe was a man who could not tell right from wrong", "because he believed the answer should be in his favor", "because he believed Farmer Joe could not remember what he had said at the scene"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3487, "question": "A family story is like a puzzle. Each family member leaves some clues. Family members come together because they have a common tie with one another, sharing a name and special traditions. Exploring family roots and sharing past memories ensure each tradition lives on. Ancestory.com has created customized \"Our Name is History\" books to give your family a look into your history by learning about your last name. By visiting _ , you can check if information is available for your last name. Ancestory.com researchers have collected more than 5 billion names from records such as passenger lists, immigration records and from birth, marriage and death records. The collected information is then used for each customized book. \"Our Name is History\" books are available for nearly 200,000 last names, ac...\n\nQ: The \"Our Name is History\" books   _  .", "options": ["are very cheap compared with flowers or jewelry", "can tell us where we should look to find out family history", "cover the last names of all Americans", "can tell us origins of our last names"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2651, "question": "Kabul,Oct.28 (Xinhuanet)--- Unknown armed men in military uniform kidnapped three staff of the United Nations in the Afghan capital city at broad daylight Thursday ,Afghan officials confirmed . \"Three armed men in military uniform _ a UN car in Baraki area ofprefix = st1 /Kabulcity early afternoon and took away three persons including two women with them, \"Rohullah, a witness at the site told Xinhua. The kidnappers also badly beat up the Afghan driver of the UN car, added Rohullah who is a lorry driver in the city. The area has been watched over by UN guards. UN officials as well as Afghan confirmed the incident but refused to provide further information. The three kidnapped , according to some officials , who are from Britain, Ireland and Kosovo, were working for the UN-sponsored Joint El...\n\nQ: When did this kidnapping take place?", "options": ["At night", "In the daytime", "Early in the morning", "at dawn"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 157, "question": "Golf in the USA was until quite recently the hobby of old,middle class white men.Not any more.The fact that the class,age and race barriers that existed in the sport have finally been broken down is due almost entirely to two people.Tiger Woods and Michelle Wie. Tiger Woods was born in California in 1975 and is one of the greatest golfers of all time.His ethnic background is marvelously rich and varied.His father Earl was of mixed of black,Chinese and Native American ancestry and his mother Kultida,who was originally from Thailand,also had Chinese and Dutch forefathers. Woods became a professional golfer in 1996 and,less than a year later,astonished the world easily winning the prestigious Masters Colf Tournament,an annual event which takes place at the Augusta Golf Club in Georgia,USA.At ...\n\nQ: What is the text about?", "options": ["Tiger Woods'life in playing golf.", "The achievements of two golf players from ethnic minorities.", "Michelle Wie's determination.", "Playing golf in USA was once the hobby of old,middle class while men."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2592, "question": "Sometimes it is difficult to talk to taxi drivers. They must give all their attention to the road as they work out the shortest way to the place where you are going. However, passengers from Wangfujing were in surprise when they took a taxi. The driver just would not stop talking - in English. Organized by the Cultural and Education Section of the British Embassy, \"Dare to Speak\" examines if Chinese people will speak English in \"real-life\" situations. Matthew Knowles, an acting student from South Carolina at Beijing Film Academy, acted the part as the \"driver\". He collected six passengers on Saturday morning, most of whom were female white-collar workers. \"Of course they were surprised at first, wondering why I'm driving a taxi, and wondering whether this is a real taxi, but then most of t...\n\nQ: Why did Matthew Knowles drive a taxi?", "options": ["He took part in the project \"Dear to speak\"", "He played the role of a taxi driver in a film.", "He enjoyed chatting with people in English.", "He wanted to improve his Chinese while driving."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3220, "question": "Thomas Brodie-Sangster's cars and action figures weren't just toys. \"They would always be characters, and I would always put on stupid voices,\" says Thomas (Born on 16 May 1990). For him, acting was just a matter of moving childhood games to a set. Maturity and independence came to Thomas early as he started work at ten. After his first audition , he learned about _ . Though hurt and disappointed, he took a part in a tiny, unknown TV film in 2001. No one noticed his performance - no one except screenwriter Richard Curtis. Two years later, he played Sam, a twelve-year-old in love in Curtis's Love Actually. After that hit film, he played actor Colin Firth's son in Nanny McPhee. Firth then joined a film called The Last Legion and supported Thomas for its lead role. As a result, the boy played...\n\nQ: Thomas Brodie-Sangster reached maturity early probably because of   _  .", "options": ["his failure in the first audition", "his starting acting as early as ten", "his being supported by adult actors", "his acting in a tiny unknown TV film"], "answer": 1}]